Guide to the James Beard Foundation Archive 1939-2008 (bulk 1990-2008) MSS.214
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Wine
  - Gabriel & Andrew, undated (Box 50, Folder 50)
  - Gabrielli Winery, undated (Box 50, Folder 51)
  - Gallo of Sonoma, undated (Box 50, Folder 52a)
  - German, Jay, undated (Box 50, Folder 52b)
  - German-Robin, Hubert, undated (Box 50, Folder 52c)
  - Gett, Steve, undated (Box 50, Folder 52d)
  - Geyser Peak Winery, undated (Box 50, Folder 53)
  - Gloag, Matthew, undated (Box 50, Folder 54)
  - Golan Heights Winery, undated (Box 50, Folder 55)
  - Graziano, Greg, undated (Box 50, Folder 56)
  - "Great European Wines of the Decade", undated (Box 50, Folder 57)
  - Green, Michael, undated (Box 50, Folder 58)
  - Gristina Vineyards, undated (Box 50, Folder 59)
  - Grochau Cellars, undated (Box 50, Folder 60)
  - Groth Winery, undated (Box 50, Folder 61)
  - Guthrie, Wells, undated (Box 50, Folder 62)
  - Hal Wine Merchants, undated (Box 50, Folder 63)
  - Hamington, Greg, undated (Box 50, Folder 64)
  - Harrison, Michael and Lindsey, undated (Box 50, Folder 65)
  - Heidsieck, Charles, undated (Box 50, Folder 66)
  - Heitz Cellars, undated (Box 50, Folder 67)
  - Heitz, Joseph, undated (Box 50, Folder 68)
  - Hendry Winery, undated (Box 50, Folder 69)
  - Herzog, undated (Box 50, Folder 70)
  - The Hess Collection Winery, undated (Box 50, Folder 71)
  - Hewiston, Dean, undated (Box 50, Folder 72)
  - Hill, William Henry, undated (Box 50, Folder 73)
  - Hindy, Stephen (Brooklyn Brewery), undated (Box 50, Folder 74)
  - Hiram Walker, undated (Box 50, Folder 75)
  - Hirmer, Gerhard, undated (Box 50, Folder 76)
  - Hitching Post Winery, undated (Box 50, Folder 77)
  - Hogue Cellars, undated (Box 50, Folder 78)
  - Honig, Michael, undated (Box 50, Folder 79)
  - Hope Estate Wines, undated (Box 50, Folder 80)
  - House of Osbourne, undated (Box 50, Folder 81)
  - Immer, Andrea, undated (Box 50, Folder 82)
  - Inniskillin, undated (Box 50, Folder 83)
  - The Institute of Masters of Wine, undated (Box 50, Folder 84)
  - Iron Horse, undated (Box 50, Folder 85)
  - Iron Stone Vineyards, undated (Box 50, Folder 86)
  - Jack Daniel Distillery, undated (Box 50, Folder 87)
  - Jackson Triggs, undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Jacob, Stacie (Wine Speaker), 2005-2007 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Johannes, Daniel, undated (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Johnson, Craig, 2005-2007 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Hugh, undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Jordan Winery, undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Justin Vineyards and Winery, undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Kendall-Jackson Vineyards, undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - King Estate, undated (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - King, Karen, undated (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Kobrand Corp., undated (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Konstantin Frank Winecellars, undated (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Kornell, Paula, undated (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Krankl, Manfred, undated (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Krug, undated (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Lake, James, undated (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Lambron, Bob, undated (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Lange Winery, undated (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Larcade, Michel, undated (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Larchet, John, undated (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Lava Cap Winery, undated (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - L'Avaneir Estate, undated (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - L'Aventure Winery, undated (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Lenz, undated (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Levin, Larry, undated (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Lingenfelder, Rainer, undated (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Lolonis Winery, undated (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Long, Zelma, undated (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Lurton, undated (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Lyeth Winery, undated (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Lynch, Kermit, undated (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Lynch, Reinhardt, undated (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Magrez, Bernard, undated (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Maison Louis Jadot, undated (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Maker's Mark Distillery, undated (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Mariani-May, Christine, undated (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Markowski, Phil, undated (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - Martha Clara Vineyards, undated (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - Martini & Rossi, undated (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Matanza's Creek Winery, undated (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - Matheson, Hugo and Kimbal Musk, undated (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - Matthewson, Mark, undated (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - Maui's Winery, undated (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - Mendocino Winegrower's Alliance, undated (Box 51, Folder 44)
  - Midolini Vineyards, undated (Box 51, Folder 45)
  - Miner Family Vineyards, undated (Box 51, Folder 46)
  - Moet & Chandon, undated (Box 51, Folder 47)
  - Robert Mondavi Wines, undated (Box 51, Folder 48)
  - Monstanto, undated (Box 51, Folder 49)
  - Moore, Gregory, undated (Box 51, Folder 50)
  - Morgan Winery, undated (Box 51, Folder 51)
  - Morrell, Peter, undated (Box 51, Folder 52)
  - Morrell Wine Bar, undated (Box 51, Folder 53)
  - Morrisey, Kevin, undated (Box 51, Folder 54)
  - Morrison Bowmore, undated (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - Mount Eden Vineyards, undated (Box 51, Folder 56a)
  - Napa Valley Wine Train, 2000-2001 (Box 51, Folder 56b)
  - Navarro Vineyards, undated (Box 51, Folder 57a)
  - Niebaum-Coppola, undated (Box 51, Folder 57b)
  - Newton Vineyard, undated (Box 51, Folder 58)
  - Nickel, Erik, undated (Box 51, Folder 59)
  - Noe, Booker, undated (Box 51, Folder 60)
  - Normandie Import, undated (Box 51, Folder 61)
  - O'Connor, Robin Kelley, undated (Box 51, Folder 62)
  - Old Vines Wine Cellars, undated (Box 51, Folder 63)
  - Oliver, Garret, undated (Box 51, Folder 64)
  - Ommegang, undated (Box 51, Folder 65)
  - Oregon Wine, undated (Box 51, Folder 66)
  - Palace Brands Company, undated (Box 51, Folder 67)
  - Palm Bay, undated (Box 51, Folder 68)
  - Parker, Robert, undated (Box 51, Folder 69)
  - Paul Hobbs Winery, undated (Box 51, Folder 70)
  - Peay Vineyards, undated (Box 51, Folder 71)
  - Peconika, undated (Box 51, Folder 72)
  - Pellegrini Family Vineyards, undated (Box 51, Folder 73)
  - Pepper Bridge Winery, undated (Box 51, Folder 74)
  - Pere Magloire Caludos, undated (Box 51, Folder 75)
  - Perrier-Jouet, undated (Box 51, Folder 76)
  - Phelps, Joseph, undated (Box 51, Folder 77)
  - Picciotto Esses, Rafael, undated (Box 51, Folder 78)
  - Pigott, Stuart, undated (Box 51, Folder 79a)
  - Pikes Wine, undated (Box 51, Folder 79b)
  - Pinar Vineyards, undated (Box 51, Folder 80)
  - Pine Ridge Winery, undated (Box 51, Folder 81)
  - Poniatowski, Prince Phillipe, undated (Box 51, Folder 82)
  - Pio Cesare Winery, undated (Box 51, Folder 83)
  - Piper Sonoma, undated (Box 51, Folder 84)
  - Ponzi Vineyard, undated (Box 51, Folder 85)
  - Portland Indie Wine Festival, undated (Box 51, Folder 86)
  - Prather, Jeff, undated (Box 51, Folder 87)
  - Pride Mountain Vineyards, undated (Box 51, Folder 88)
  - Pyramid Aces, undated (Box 51, Folder 89)
  - Ravenswood, undated (Box 51, Folder 90)
  - Reichscgraf Von Kesselstatt, undated (Box 51, Folder 91)
  - Reis, Pedro Silva, undated (Box 51, Folder 92)
  - Remy Martin, undated (Box 51, Folder 93)
  - Ridge Vineyards, undated (Box 51, Folder 94)
  - Rioja Winery, undated (Box 51, Folder 95)
  - Rhebokskloof Estate, undated (Box 51, Folder 96)
  - Robinson, Jancis, undated (Box 51, Folder 97)
  - Roederer Chapagne, undated (Box 51, Folder 98)
  - Rombauer, Koerner, undated (Box 51, Folder 99)
  - Rosemount Estate (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Rosset, Fabrice (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Row Eleven Wine Co. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Sagponack Vineyards, undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - St. Francis Vineyard, undated (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - St. Supery, undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Sakonnet Vineyards, undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Salud, undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Sandeman, David P., undated (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Sonoma Valley, undated (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Santa Julia Vineyards, undated (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Saunders, Audrey, undated (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Scharffenburger Cellars, undated (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Schramsberg Vineyards, undated (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Scicolone, Charles, undated (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - The Scotch Malt Whiskey Society, undated (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Scott Street Portfolio, undated (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Seagrams, undated (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Selene Wines, undated (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Sequoia Grove, undated (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Sere, Melissa, undated (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Shafer Vineyards, undated (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Shinn Estate Vineyards, undated (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Sichel, Peter, undated (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Simi Winery, undated (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Southcorp, undated (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Spellman, Joseph, undated (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Spottswoode, undated (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Staglin Family Vineyard, undated (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Stag's Leap, undated (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Stark, Dick, undated (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - Steele Wines, undated (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - Stella and Mosca Wines, undated (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Steltzner Vineyards, undated (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - Sterling Vineyard, undated (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - Stone Hill Winery, undated (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - Stonegate Winery, undated (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - Summers, Robert, undated (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - Swanson Vineyards, undated (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - Tablas Creek Vineyards, undated (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - Talbott Vineyards, undated (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - Tattinger, undated (Box 52, Folder 42)
  - Tchelistcheff, Andre, undated (Box 52, Folder 43)
  - Test, Stephen, undated (Box 52, Folder 44)
  - Teton Glacier Vodka, undated (Box 52, Folder 45)
  - Thackery, Sean, undated (Box 52, Folder 46)
  - Theise, Terry, undated (Box 52, Folder 47)
  - Thompson, David, undated (Box 52, Folder 48)
  - Thoreen, John, undated (Box 52, Folder 49)
  - Thorton Winery, undated (Box 52, Folder 50)
  - Tiefenbrunner, undated (Box 52, Folder 51)
  - Tish, W.R., undated (Box 52, Folder 52)
  - Trefethen Vineyards, undated (Box 52, Folder 53)
  - Tresher, Greg, undated (Box 52, Folder 54)
  - Triffon, Madeline, undated (Box 52, Folder 55)
  - Trinchero Family Estate, undated (Box 52, Folder 56)
  - Tuley, Helen, undated (Box 52, Folder 57)
  - Upchurch, Chris, undated (Box 52, Folder 58)
  - Vanberg and Dewulf, undated (Box 52, Folder 59)
  - Vaughn, Michael Bryan, undated (Box 52, Folder 60)
  - Vecino, Concha, undated (Box 52, Folder 61)
  - Veenwouden, undated (Box 52, Folder 62)
  - Venetian Wine, undated (Box 52, Folder 63a)
  - Veuve Chiquot, undated (Box 52, Folder 63b)
  - Villa Cafaggio, undated (Box 52, Folder 64)
  - Villa Frattina, undated (Box 52, Folder 65)
  - Vina Carmen Wines, undated (Box 52, Folder 66)
  - Vina Morande, undated (Box 52, Folder 67)
  - Von Ortloff, undated (Box 52, Folder 68)
  - Walter, Mark, undated (Box 52, Folder 69)
  - Washington Wine Commission, undated (Box 52, Folder 70)
  - Weingut Robert Weil, undated (Box 52, Folder 71)
  - Wente Brothers Winery, undated (Box 52, Folder 72.)
  - Wente, Carolyn, undated (Box 52, Folder 73)
  - Westport River Winery, undated (Box 52, Folder 74)
  - White, Ellen, undated (Box 52, Folder 73)
  - Whitehall Vineyards, undated (Box 52, Folder 74)
  - Whitehouse-Crawford, undated (Box 52, Folder 75)
  - Willakenzie Estate, undated (Box 52, Folder 76)
  - William Hill Estate, undated (Box 52, Folder 77)
  - William Wheeler Winery, undated (Box 52, Folder 78)
  - Winiarski, Warren, undated (Box 52, Folder 79)
  - Wolffer Estate, undated (Box 52, Folder 80)
  - Woodford Reserve, undated (Box 52, Folder 81)
  - Zaca Mesa, undated (Box 52, Folder 82)
  - Zeiger, Chet, undated (Box 52, Folder 83)
  - Zraly, Kevin, undated (Box 52, Folder 84)
- Series II: Wine (flat box)
  - Antinori, Piero, November 28, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 1, Box data_value_missing_7b56a65af3a1665f8f4dd1e259259a60)
  - Bespaloff, Alexis, [undated] (Box 58, Folder 2, Box data_value_missing_65a6276c1721e582e69122236dc97811)
  - Carney, Scott, March 2, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 3, Box data_value_missing_4b05cf8f1fab518feacd2cbd4ca18386)
  - Gallo, Ernest, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 4, Box data_value_missing_b8515d616040a40ada057ee3cd2d0d66)
  - Phillips, William, March 2, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 5, Box data_value_missing_15c97b6abf10270009da5d177a3734cd)
  - Santa Julia Wines, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 6, Box data_value_missing_4151a73fb166760b7c2e412b7add98fa)
  - Wine- Miscellaneous, April 10, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 7, Box data_value_missing_60cddfcac59d29bfb45e6e2801355589)
- Series III: Food Writers and Personalities
  - Acheson, Hugh, undated (Box 52, Folder 85)
  - Adams, Marcia, undated (Box 52, Folder 86)
  - Adrian, Pat, undated (Box 52, Folder 87)
  - Alex, Kathie, undated (Box 52, Folder 88)
  - Alexander, Merle, undated (Box 52, Folder 89)
  - Allen, Draina, undated (Box 52, Folder 90)
  - Altman, Joey, undated (Box 52, Folder 90)
  - American Culinary Federation, 1997-1998 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Amuerza, Clara Maria, undated (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Anderson, Burton, undated (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Anderson, Jean, undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Andrews, Andrew, undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Andrews, Colman, undated (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Appleton Voltz, Jeanne, undated (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Artise, John Anthony, undated (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Atkins, Robert, undated (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Auchmutey, Jim, undated (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Bailey, Lee, undated (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Baird, Pat, undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Baker, Leslie, undated (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Balsey, Betty, undated (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Barnard, Melanie, undated (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Barron, Rosemary, undated (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Barry, Lynda, undated (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Bates, Caroline, undated (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Batterberry, Michael, undated (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Batz. Jeanette, undated (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Bauer, Michael, undated (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Beck, Bruce, undated (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Beck, Michael, undated (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Beck, Simone, undated (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Becker, Ethan, undated (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Becker, Rene, undated (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Behr, Edward, undated (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Belk, Sarah, undated (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Beranbaum, Rose Levy, undated (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Bergeron, Ken, undated (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Berns, Herman Jerome, undated (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Bettoja, Jo, undated (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Biggers, Sissy, undated (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Biondi, Piero, undated (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Bissell, Franus, undated (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Bittman, Mark, undated (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Black, Bonnie Lee, undated (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Blonz, Ed, undated (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - Bodger, Corraine, undated (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - Boggs, Bill, undated (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - Bon Appetit, undated (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - Bonadies, Michael, undated (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - Bond, Jules, undated (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - Bourg, Gene, undated (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - Bowers, David, undated (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - Brainard, John, undated (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - Braker, Flo, undated (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - Brennan, Georgeanne, undated (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - Brennan, Kathleen, undated (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - Brenner, Leslie, undated (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - Brithcky, Seymore, undated (Box 53, Folder 51)
  - Brock, Carol, undated (Box 53, Folder 52)
  - Brody, Jane E., undated (Box 53, Folder 53)
  - Brody, Jerome, undated (Box 53, Folder 54)
  - Brown, Philip, undated (Box 53, Folder 55)
  - Brownstone, Cecily, undated (Box 53, Folder 56)
  - Bryson, Bill, undated (Box 53, Folder 57)
  - Bugialli, Giuliano, undated (Box 53, Folder 58)
  - Buller, Michael, undated (Box 53, Folder 59)
  - Burgess, Linda, undated (Box 53, Folder 60)
  - Burns, Gene, undated (Box 53, Folder 61)
  - Burns, Robert, undated (Box 53, Folder 62)
  - Burros, Marian, undated (Box 53, Folder 63)
  - Callahan, Chad, undated (Box 53, Folder 64)
  - Callen, Anna Teresa, undated (Box 53, Folder 65)
  - Cane, David Michael, undated (Box 53, Folder 66)
  - Capp, Karen, undated (Box 53, Folder 67)
  - Careme, Marie-Antoine, undated (Box 53, Folder 68)
  - Carpernter, Hugh, undated (Box 53, Folder 69)
  - Carper, Jean, undated (Box 53, Folder 70)
  - Casas, Penelope, undated (Box 53, Folder 71)
  - Chalmers, Irena, undated (Box 53, Folder 72)
  - Chamberlain, Narcisse, undated (Box 53, Folder 73a)
  - Chef Miles, undated (Box 53, Folder 73b)
  - Chen, Helen, undated (Box 53, Folder 74)
  - Chen, Joyce, undated (Box 53, Folder 75)
  - Chi, Tony, undated (Box 53, Folder 76)
  - Chin, Wanda (and Michael Danowski), undated (Box 53, Folder 77)
  - Chirls, Pamela, undated (Box 53, Folder 78)
  - Choate, Judith, undated (Box 53, Folder 79)
  - Chrichton, Ginger Munsch, undated (Box 53, Folder 80)
  - Cipriani, Arrigo, undated (Box 53, Folder 81)
  - Claiborne, Craig, undated (Box 53, Folder 82)
  - Clancy, John, undated (Box 53, Folder 83)
  - Claridge, Laurann, undated (Box 53, Folder 84)
  - Clarke, Austin, undated (Box 53, Folder 85)
  - Clarke, Oz, undated (Box 53, Folder 86)
  - Clingerman, Polly, undated (Box 53, Folder 87)
  - Coe, Sophie, undated (Box 53, Folder 88)
  - Conte, Anne Del, undated (Box 53, Folder 89)
  - Cook, Alison, undated (Box 53, Folder 90)
  - Corcoran, Penelope, undated (Box 53, Folder 91)
  - Corn, Elaine, undated (Box 53, Folder 92)
  - Cousineau, Ruth, undated (Box 53, Folder 93)
  - Coulsen, Ellen, undated (Box 53, Folder 94)
  - Cunningham, Marion, undated (Box 53, Folder 95)
  - Curry, Brother Rick, undated (Box 53, Folder 96)
  - Cusick, Heidy Haughty, undated (Box 53, Folder 97)
  - Daley, Regan, undated (Box 53, Folder 98)
  - Damerow, Gail, undated (Box 53, Folder 99)
  - Davenberg, Linda, undated (Box 53, Folder 100)
  - David, Elizabeth, undated (Box 53, Folder 101)
  - Davids, Kenneth, undated (Box 53, Folder 102)
  - Davidson, Alan, undated (Box 53, Folder 103)
  - Davidson, Suzy, undated (Box 53, Folder 104)
  - Davis, Amy, undated (Box 53, Folder 105)
  - de Blasi, Manena, undated (Box 53, Folder 106)
  - Della Croce, Julia, undated (Box 53, Folder 107)
  - Devi, Yamuna, undated (Box 53, Folder 108)
  - DeWitt, Dave, undated (Box 53, Folder 109)
  - Dille, Carolyn, undated (Box 53, Folder 110)
  - Dionot, Francois, undated (Box 53, Folder 111)
  - Dodge, Jim, undated (Box 53, Folder 112)
  - Dojny, Brooke, undated (Box 53, Folder 113)
  - Dolinsky, Steve, undated (Box 53, Folder 114)
  - Dornenburg, Andrew and Karen Page, undated (Box 53, Folder 115)
  - Downard, Georgia, undated (Box 53, Folder 116)
  - Drower, Sara, undated (Box 53, Folder 117)
  - Drummond, Geoffrey, undated (Box 53, Folder 118)
  - Duguid, Naomi, undated (Box 53, Folder 119)
  - Duijker, Hubrecht, undated (Box 53, Folder 120)
  - Dunaway, Suzanne, undated (Box 53, Folder 121)
  - Dupree, Nathalee, undated (Box 53, Folder 122)
  - Durbin, Barbara, undated (Box 53, Folder 123)
  - Duval, Logan, undated (Box 53, Folder 124)
  - D'Vari, Marisa, undated (Box 53, Folder 125)
  - Eckerle, Tom, undated (Box 53, Folder 126)
  - Eddy, Kristin, undated (Box 53, Folder 127)
  - Edelman, Julie, undated (Box 53, Folder 128)
  - Eliot, Peter, undated (Box 53, Folder 129)
  - Ellis, Jane, undated (Box 53, Folder 130)
  - Ellis, Merle, undated (Box 53, Folder 131)
  - Elman-Winston, Dorthea, undated (Box 53, Folder 132)
  - Escoffier, Auguste, undated (Box 53, Folder 133)
  - Esposito, Mary Ann, undated (Box 53, Folder 134)
  - Evans, Michelle, undated (Box 53, Folder 135)
  - Fabricant, Florence, undated (Box 53, Folder 136)
  - Famularo, Joe, undated (Box 53, Folder 137)
  - Farmer, Fannie, undated (Box 53, Folder 138)
  - Feder, Penny, undated (Box 53, Folder 139)
  - Feretti, Fred, undated (Box 53, Folder 140)
  - Field, Carol, undated (Box 53, Folder 141)
  - Fisher, M.F.K., undated (Box 53, Folder 142)
  - Fitch, Noel Riley, undated (Box 53, Folder 143)
  - Fletcher, Janet, undated (Box 53, Folder 144)
  - Florence, Tyler, undated (Box 53, Folder 145)
  - Fobel, Jim, undated (Box 53, Folder 146)
  - Fowler, Damon, undated (Box 53, Folder 147)
  - Fox, Jeanne, undated (Box 53, Folder 148)
  - Franey, Pierre, undated (Box 53, Folder 149)
  - Fredericks, Lynn, undated (Box 53, Folder 150)
  - Freiman, Jane, undated (Box 53, Folder 151)
  - Friedrich, Jacqueline, undated (Box 53, Folder 152)
  - Fussel, Betty, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Ganga, Stone, December 15, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 1a, Box data_value_missing_cde0f8c120358a15ef0de7179ab5a8f1)
  - Garry, William, undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Gassenheimer, Linda, undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Gelles, Carol, undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Gibson, Charles, undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Geidt, Frances Tower, undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Gilberti, Ben, undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Giobbi, Edward, undated (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Giuliani, Donna Hanover, undated (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Glaser, Milton, undated (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Gold, Rozanne, undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Gocs, Miles Lambert, undated (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Goldstein, Kay, [undated] (Box 54, Folder 12a, Box data_value_missing_cdf6d467ef8c9d99ede2a0d1ec3107ff)
  - Graff, Richard, undated (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Graham, Kevin, undated (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Grand Central Market, undated (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Grausman, Richard, undated (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Gray, Todd, undated (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Greco, Gail, undated (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Greene, Bert, undated (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Greene, Gael, undated (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Greenstein, George, undated (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Greer, Anne Lindsay, undated (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Grey, Joel, undated (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Griffith, Linda and Fred, undated (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Grigson, Sophie, undated (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Griscom, Nina, undated (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Grosnevor, Vertamae, undated (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Guarnaschelli, Maria, undated (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Gugnio, Sam, undated (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Haber, Barbara, undated (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Haeger, John, undated (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Halm, Meesha, undated (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Hamilton D'Ana, DeAnne, undated (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - Hamilton, Dorothy, undated (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - Hammersley, Fiona McLaren, undated (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - Hanes, Phyllis, undated (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Hanle, Zack, undated (Box 54, Folder 37)
  - Hard, Amelia, undated (Box 54, Folder 38)
  - Harlow, Jay, undated (Box 54, Folder 39)
  - Harron, Hallie, undated (Box 54, Folder 40)
  - Hartz, Deborah, undated (Box 54, Folder 41)
  - Harvey, Frederick, undated (Box 54, Folder 42)
  - Hayes, Joanna Lamb, undated (Box 54, Folder 43)
  - Hazan, Giuliano, undated (Box 54, Folder 44)
  - Hazan, Marcella, undated (Box 54, Folder 45)
  - Hazard, Jan Turner, undated (Box 54, Folder 46)
  - Healy, Bruce, undated (Box 54, Folder 47)
  - Heatter, Maida, undated (Box 54, Folder 48)
  - Hemingway, Mary, undated (Box 54, Folder 49)
  - Henderson, Janice Wald, undated (Box 54, Folder 50)
  - Henderson, Ruth Skitch, undated (Box 54, Folder 51)
  - Herbst, Sharon Tyler, undated (Box 54, Folder 52)
  - Hess, Mary Abbott, undated (Box 54, Folder 53)
  - Hibler, Janie, undated (Box 54, Folder 54)
  - Hillman, Libby, undated (Box 54, Folder 55)
  - Hiser, Elizabeth, undated (Box 54, Folder 56)
  - Hoffman, Mable, undated (Box 54, Folder 57)
  - Holzinger, Steve, undated (Box 54, Folder 58)
  - Hooker, Monique, undated (Box 54, Folder 59)
  - Hoppin' John, undated (Box 54, Folder 60)
  - Horn, Jane, undated (Box 54, Folder 61)
  - Howden, Duncan, undated (Box 54, Folder 62)
  - Howkins, Mary Ann, undated (Box 54, Folder 63)
  - Hunter, Kellye, undated (Box 54, Folder 64)
  - Hutson, Lucinda, undated (Box 54, Folder 65)
  - Iggers, Jeremy, undated (Box 54, Folder 66)
  - In Pursuit of Tea, undated (Box 54, Folder 67)
  - Jackson, Michael, undated (Box 54, Folder 68)
  - Jacobsen, Eric, undated (Box 54, Folder 69)